《邪恶力量》
（堪萨斯州 劳伦斯市 22年前）
来向你弟弟说晚安
Come on, let's say good night to your brother.
- 晚安 萨姆 - 晚安 宝贝
- 'Night Sam. - Good night, love.
嘿 迪恩
Hey! Dean.
- 爸爸 - 小伙子
- Daddy! - Hey! Buddy.
你怎么看 萨姆可以打橄榄球了吗
What do you think? Sam is ready to touch around football yet?
- 不行 爸爸 - 不行吗
- No, daddy. - No?
- 你来照顾他 - 好的
- You got him? - I got him.
做个好梦 萨米
Sweet dreams, Sammy.
约翰
John?
约翰 他是不是饿了
John, is he hungry?
好吧
Okay.
萨米
Sammy!
玛丽
Mary!
萨米
Hey, Sammy.
还好吗
Okay?
不 玛丽
No! Mary!
爸爸
Daddy!
赶快把你弟弟带到外面去
Take your brother outside as fast as you can!
不要回头看
Don't look back!
快点 迪恩 快跑
Now, Dean! Go!
玛丽
Mary!
不
No!
没事的 萨米
It's okay, Sammy.
我来 去救火
I got it. Go put the fire now.
给
Here.
往后站 你们得往后站
Stay back. You have to stay back.
（斯坦福大学 现今）
萨姆
Sam!
快点好吗
Get a move on, would ya?
我们应该15分钟前就到那了
We were supposed to be there like 15 minutes ago.
萨姆 你去还是不去啊
Sam, you coming or what?
- 我必须得去吗 - 是的 会很有趣的
- Do I have to? - Yes. It'll be fun.
怎么不化妆
And where's your costume?
你知道我对万圣节的感觉
You know how I feel about Halloween.
祝贺萨姆和他法学院入学考试的高分
So here's to Sam and his awesome LSAT victory.
好的 好的 这没什么大不了的
All right, all right. It's not that big a deal.
他看上去谦虚 但是他考了174分
Yeah, he acts all humble, but he scored a 174.
- 算高分吗 - 高得吓人了
- Is that good? - Scary good.
瞧啊 名校任你选了
See, there you go. You are a first-round draft pick.
想进哪个法学院都可以
You can go to any law school you want.
实际上 我这周一就有个面试
Actually, I got an interview here monday.
如果顺利 我想我明年有机会拿全金
If it goes okay, I think I got a shot at a full ride next year.
肯定会顺利的
Hey, it's gonna go great.
但愿吧
It better.
成为家中的金童感觉怎样
How does it feel to be the golden boy in your family?
他们不知道
They don't know.
不知道 要是我早美到天上了 干嘛不说
No? I would be gloating. Why not?
因为我们不是脱线家族
Because we're not exactly the Bradys.
我也不是天才老爹家的
I'm not exactly the Huxtables.
再喝点
More shots?
- 不了 - 不 不用
- No. - No. No.
说真的 我为你感到骄傲
Seriously, I'm proud of you,
周一你肯定让他们大吃一惊
And you're gonna knock them dead on monday.
你会拿全额奖学金的
You're gonna get that full ride.
我知道
I know it.
没有你我该怎么办
What would I do without you?
为爱神伤吧
Crash and burn.
放松 小老虎
Whoa! Easy, tiger.
迪恩
Dean?
你吓死我了
You scared the crap out of me.
那是因为你荒废了功夫
That's cause you're out of practice.
看来没有
Or not.
放开我
Get off of me.
迪恩 你来这里到底要干什么
Dean, what the hell are you doing here?
我来找啤酒
I was looking for a beer.
你到底要干嘛
What the hell are you doing here?
好吧 我们得谈谈
Ok, all right, we got to talk.
- 电话里不能说吗 - 我打你会接吗
- The phone? - If I'd called would you picked up?
萨姆
Sam?
杰西
Jess, hey.
迪恩 这是我的女朋友杰西卡
Dean, this is my girlfriend, Jessica.
等等 他是你哥哥迪恩
Wait. Your brother Dean?
我喜欢蓝精灵
I love the Smurfs.
知道吗 我得说
You know, I got to tell you.
我弟弟真配不上你
You are completely out of my brother's league.
我穿下衣服
Just let me put something on.
别别 我不会胡思乱想的 真的
No, no. No, I wouldn't dream of it, seriously.
总之 我借你男朋友一用
Anyway, I got to borrow your boyfriend here,
谈点家里私事
talk about some private family business,
很高兴见到你
but nice meeting you.
不不 无论你想说什么 她都可以听
No. No, whatever you want to say, you can say it in front of her.
好吧
Okay.
爸爸好几天不在家了
Dad hasn't been home in a few days.
这怎么了 他在「米勒时间」加班呢
So? He's working overtime on a "Miller Time" shift.
他迟早会回来的
He'll stumble back in sooner or later.
他外出狩猎 几天过去迟迟未归
Dad's on a hunting trip, and he hasn't been home in a few days.
杰西 失陪一下
Jess, excuse us.
我们要出去说
We have to go outside.
我说 你不要半夜突然跑来
I mean, come on, you can't just break in the middle of the night.
让我和你一起出去
and expect me to hit the road with you.
你没有听懂我的意思 萨姆 爸爸失踪了
You're not hearing me, Sammy. Dad's missing.
我需要你帮我找他
I need you to help me find him.
你还记得阿姆赫斯特的捣蛋鬼
You remember the poltergeist in Amherst,
还有克利夫顿的魔鬼之门吗
or the devil's gates in Clifton?
那两次他不也是失踪了
He was missing then, too.
他总是失踪 可又总是好好的
He's always missing, and he's always fine.
但是从没这么久 现在你跟不跟我走
Not for this long. Now, are you gonna come with me or not?
不去
I'm not.
为什么不去
Why not?
我发过誓再也不去抓鬼了 永远不去
I swore I was done hunting. For good.
行了 我们属实不易
Come on, it wasn't easy,
- 但也没那么糟糕 - 是吗
- but it wasn't that bad. - Yeah?
小时候我告诉爸爸我害怕衣柜里有怪物
When I told dad I was scared of the thing in my closet,
他却给我一支点45手枪
he gave me a.45.
那他应该怎么做
What was he supposed to do?
我那时才9岁
I was 9 years old.
他应该说「别怕黑」
He was supposed to say: "Don't be afraid of the dark."
「别怕黑」 你逗我玩呢
"Don't be afraid of the dark"? Are you kidding me?
你当然应当怕黑 你知道黑暗里有什么
Of course, you should be afraid. You know what's out there.
我知道 但是妈妈被杀后我们那种成长方式
Yeah I know but still… the way we grew up after mom was killed.
爸爸着魔似地寻找杀死妈妈的那个东西
and dad's obsession to find the thing that killed her.
但我们还没有找到那个该死的东西
But we still haven't found the damn thing.
所以我们杀死能够找到的一切
So we kill everything we can find.
这样做也救了很多人啊
Save a lot of people doing it, too.
你觉得妈妈会希望我们这样吗
You think mom would have wanted this for us?
练习使用武器 给子弹里灌银
The weapon training and melting the silver into bullets?
迪恩 我们的成长历程完全是战士的生活
Man, Dean, we were raised like warriors.
那你想怎样
So, what are you gonna do?
你想过那种正常的美国式生活
Are you just gonna live some normal, apple-pie life?
是吗
Is that it?
不 不是正常的 是安全的
No, not normal. Safe.
这就是你离家的原因
And that's why you ran away.
我原本只是想上大学
I was just going to college.
是爸爸说如果我要走 就永远别回去
It was dad who said if I was gonna go, I should stay gone.
我现在也不会回去
And that's what I'm doing.
爸爸现在一定遇到了大麻烦
Dad's in real trouble right now.
如果不是已经死了的话
if he's not dead already.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
我一个人不行
I can't do this alone.
你可以的
Yes, you can.
对 但我不想那样
Yeah. Well, I don't want to.
他追捕的是什么
What was he hunting?
让我想想 我到底把它放哪了
All right. Let's see. Where the hell did I put that thing?
爸爸走的时候 你怎么不跟他去
So when dad left, why didn't you go with him?
我有自己的活儿
I was working my own gig…
新奥尔良一桩巫毒事件
This voodoo thing down in New Orleans.
爸爸让你独自抓鬼
Dad let you go on a hunting trip by yourself?
我26岁了 伙计
I'm 26, dude.
好 找到了
All right, here we go.
爸爸在查加利福尼亚的耶利哥市郊外
So dad was checking out this two-lane blacktop.
一段双车道柏油路
just outside of Jericho, California.
一个月前 这个人
About a month ago, this guy…
有人发现了他的车 但他不见了
They found his car, but he'd vanished.
人间蒸发
Completely M.I.A.
也许他被绑架了
So maybe he was kidnapped.
有理 4月份又一起
Yeah, well, here's another one in April,
12月一起 04年 03年
another one in December '04, '03,
98年 92年 过去20年总共10起
'98, '92… 10 of them over the past 20 years…
所有人都是在同一段5英里道路上出事的
All men, all same 5-mile stretch of road.
失踪事件越来越多
Started happening more and more, so.
所以爸爸就去查了
dad went to go dig around.
大约是3周前
That was about three weeks ago.
打那以后一直没有他的消息
I hadn't heard from him since,
这就够糟糕了
which is bad enough,
昨天我又收到了这封语音邮件
And then I get this voice mail yesterday.
迪恩 有事正在发生 我觉得很严重
Dean, something is starting to happen. I think it's serious.
我得搞清楚是怎么回事
I need to try to figure out what's going on.
千万小心 迪恩 我们都很危险
Be very careful, Dean. We're all in danger.
注意到里面的超自然电子异象了吗
You know there's EVP on that?
不错嘛 萨米 有些技艺就是忘不掉哈
Not bad, Sammy. Kind of like riding a bike, isn't it?
好吧 我把它放慢
All right. I slowed the message down.
通过GoldWave软件进行处理
and ran it through a goldwave,
去掉嘶嘶声 得到了这个
took out the hiss, and this is what I got.
我永远也回不了家
I can never go home.
永远也回不了家
Never go home.
你知道吗 快两年了
You know, in almost two years,
我从未烦过你 从未要求你做任何事情
I've never bothered you, never asked you for a thing.
好 我去
All right, I'll go.
我帮你找到他
I'll help you find him,
但我周一一大早就要回来
but I have to get back first thing Monday.
在这等我
Just wait here.
周一一大早你要干嘛
What's first thing monday?
我有
I've this…
我有个面试
I have an interview.
什么 工作面试 推了
What? A job interview? Skip it.
是法学院面试 我的未来就在眼前
It's a law-school interview, and it's my whole future on a plate.
法学院
Law school?
行还是不行
So we got a deal or not?
等等 你要走
Wait, you're taking off?
是为你爸爸的事吗 他还好吗
Is this about your dad? Is he all right?
还好 家务事而已
Yeah. You know, just a little family drama.
但之前你哥哥说他外出捕猎什么的
But your brother said he was on some kind of hunting trip.
是的 他去林中小屋附近猎鹿
Yeah, he's just deer hunting up at the cabin,
八成和吉姆 杰克和乔斯一起
and he's probably got Jim, Jack, and Jose along with him.
我们去接他回来
We're just gonna go bring him back.
那面试怎么办
What about the interview?
我会去面试的
I'll make the interview.
我只去两天而已
This is only for a couple days.
萨姆 拜托 等一下
Sam, I mean, please. Just stop for a second.
你确定你没事吗
You're sure you're okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
只是 你从不提及你的家人
It's just… You want even talk about your family.
现在却要 三更半夜离开
And now you're taking off the middle of the night.
去和他们一起度周末
to spend the week-end with them.
而且周一还有要事
And with Monday coming up…
这不是你的风格
It's just not kind of your style.
一切都会好起来的
Hey, everything's gonna be okay.
我会及时回来 我保证
I would be back in time, I promise.
至少告诉我你去哪里
At least tell me where you're going!
（加利福尼亚州 耶利哥市）
艾米 我今晚不能去找你了
Amy, I can't come over tonight.
因为我明早要工作 这就是原因
Because I got work in the morning, that's why.
我要是翘班 我爸会杀了我的
Okay, I miss it, my dad's gonna have my ass.
艾米 等会我再打给你
Hey, uh, Amy, let me call you back.
车子坏了还是怎么啦
Car trouble or something?
送我回家
Take me home.
好的 上车吧
Sure, get in.
你住哪
So where do you live?
布雷肯里奇路的尽头
At the end of Breckenridge Road.
你是从万圣节派对上回来的吗
You're coming from a Halloween party or something?
知道吗 像你这样的姑娘不该一个人在外面
You know, um, a girl like you really shouldn't be alone out here.
我和你在一起
I'm with you.
你觉得我漂亮吗
Do you think I'm pretty?
和我一起回家吗
Will you come home with me?
好吧
Um…Hell, yeah.
拜托 你不会住在这里的
Come on. You don't live here.
我永远也回不了家
I can never go home.
什么 你说什么 这里没人住
What? What are you talking about? Nobody lives here.
你住哪
Huh, where do you live?
真好
That's good.
别开玩笑了 好不好
Joke's over, okay?
你想让我离开吗
You want me to leave?
有人吗
Hello?
想吃早餐吗
Hey. You want breakfast?
不 谢谢
No, thanks.
你怎么付账的
So how'd you pay for that stuff?
你和爸爸还在用信用卡欺诈吗
You and dad still running credit-card scams?
对 猎鬼的收入可跟职业篮球没法比
Yeah, well, hunting aingt exactly a pro-ball career.
还有 我们只是申请
Besides, all we do is apply.
银行寄卡过来 这又不是我们的错
It's not our fault they send us the cards.
是 这次你在申请表上填了谁的名字
Yeah, and what names did you write on the application this time?
伯特·阿法米恩和他儿子赫克托
Uh… Bert Aframian and his son, Hector.
一下办了两张卡
Scored two cards out of the deal.
听上去不错
Sounds about right.
我发誓 你得升级你的磁带收藏了
I swear, man, you got to update your cassette-tape collection.
为什么
Why?
第一 你这全是磁带
Well, for one… They're cassette tapes.
第二
And two…
黑色安息日 摩托党 金属狂热
Black Sabbath, Motorhead, Metallica?
这都是七八十年代的经典摇滚啦
It's the greatest hits of mullet rock.
老规矩 萨米 司机选音乐
House rules, Sammy… driver picks the music,
副驾驶不要插嘴
shotgun shuts his cake hole.
萨米是胖嘟嘟的12岁男孩 这也…
Yo Sammy is a chubby 12-year-old. It's…
不好意思 我听不清 音乐太响
Sorry, I can't hear you. The music's too loud.
（耶利哥市 7英里）
谢谢
Thank you.
医院和太平间没有和爸爸特征相符的人
All right. So there's no one matching dad at the hospital or morgue.
我猜这是个好消息
So that's something, I guess.
去看看什么事
Check it out.
走吧
Let's go.
你们找到什么了吗
Did you guys find anything?
没 什么也没有
No! Nothing!
没有挣扎的痕迹 没有脚印 没指纹
No sign of struggle, no footprints, no fingerprints…
没有任何痕迹 太干净了点
Spotless. It's almost too clean.
那个孩子 特洛伊
So this kid, Troy…
- 他和你女儿在约会 是吗 - 是的
- He's dating your daughter, isn't he? - Ya.
艾米怎么样
How's Amy doing?
她在市中心张贴寻人启事
She's been putting up missing posters downtown.
上个月这里也有一起类似案件 是不是
You had another one like this last month, didn't you?
你们是
And who are you?
联邦探员
Federal marshals.
作为探员 你们俩太年轻了点吧
You two are a little young for marshals, aren't you?
谢谢 你真会说话
Thanks, that's awfully kind of you.
之前有过一起类似的案件 没错吧
You did have another one just like this, correct?
是 没错
Yeah, that's right,
距这里大约1英里 之前也有好几起
About a mile up the road. There have been others before that.
那么这个受害者 你认得他
So this victim… you knew him?
像这样的小镇 大家都互相认识
A town like this, everybody knows everybody.
受害者除了都是男性之外
Any connection between the victims.
还有什么共同之处
besides that they're all men?
没了 目前还没有发现
No. Not so far as we can tell.
作案手段是什么
So what's the theory?
说实话 我们不知道
Honestly, we don't know…
连环杀手 连环绑架
Serial murderer, kidnapping ring.
我看你们这种警员
Well, that is exactly the kind of crack.
也就只能做到这种程度了
police work I'd expect out of you guys.
谢谢你的宝贵时间
Thank you for your time.
先生们
Gentlemen.
干嘛打我
What was that for?
干嘛踩我脚
Why do you have to step on my foot?
干嘛那样对警察说话
Why do you have to talk to police like that?
得了吧 他们根本不知道发生了什么
Come on. They don't really know what's going on.
我们只有靠自己
We're all alone on this.
如果我们想找到爸爸
If we're gonna find dad,
我们就要自己查清楚这件事
We've got to get to the bottom of this thing ourselves.
需要帮忙吗 孩子们
Can I help you boys?
不用 警长 我们正要走
No, sir. We were just leaving.
摩德探员 斯卡琳探员
Agent Mulder, agent Scully.
我敢打赌 就是她
I'll bet you that's her.
是啊
Yeah.
- 你一定是艾米 - 是我
- You must be Amy. - Yeah.
特洛伊和我们说过你 我们是他叔叔
Troy told us about you. We're his uncles.
我是迪恩 他是萨姆
I'm Dean. This is Sammy.
他从未向我提过你们
He never mentioned you to me.
特洛伊就是这样
Well, that's Troy, I guess.
我们不常过来 我们住在莫德斯托
We're not around much. We're up in Modesto.
其实我们也在找他 正在四处打听
So we're looking for him, too, and we're kind of asking around.
- 你还好吧 - 我没事
- Hey, are you okay? - Yeah.
你介意我们问你几个问题吗
Do you mind if we ask you a couple questions?
我当时在跟特洛伊通话 他正开车回家
I was on the phone with Troy. He was driving home.
他说很快会回电给我 但是他再也没打过
He said he would call me right back, and he never did.
那他有没有提到一些奇怪
He didn't say anything strange?
或者是不寻常的事情呢
Or out of the ordinary?
没有 我记得什么都没有说
No, nothing I can remember.
我很喜欢你的项链
I like your necklace.
特洛伊给我的
Troy gave it to me.
主要拿来吓我父母
Mostly to scare my parents…
你知道 恶魔崇拜什么的
You know, the devil stuff.
实际上这恰恰相反
Actually it means just the opposite.
五芒星是个辟邪的护身符
A pentagram is a protection against evil.
力量很强大 我是说 如果你信的话
Really powerfull, I mean if you believe in a kind of thing.
很好 谢谢主持《未解之谜》
Ok, thank you, Unsolved Mysteries.
女士们 事情是这样的
Here's the deal, ladies…
特洛伊失踪的方式很不正常
The way Troy disappeared… Something's not right.
所以要是你们听到过任何事情
So if you've heard anything…
有什么事
What is it?
这只是
Well, it's just…
关于失踪的这些人 有个传闻
I mean, with all these guys going missing, people talk.
什么传闻
What do they talk about?
是本地的一个传说
It's kind of this local legend.
有个女孩 几十年前在百年纪念路上被杀
This one girl, she got murdered out on Centennial like decades ago.
人们猜测 她一直在那儿
Well, supposedly, she's still out there.
她搭便车 不管谁让她上了车
She hitchhikes, and whoever picks her up…
都会永远消失不见
Well, they disappear forever.
（女性 谋杀 搭车）
（0个结果）
（女性 谋杀 百年纪念路）
- 让我试试 - 我能行
- Let me try. - I got it.
兄弟
Dude.
你真是个控制癖
You're such a control freak.
- 厉鬼都是横死 对吧 - 对
- So angry spirits are born out of violent death, right? - Yeah.
或许不是谋杀
Maybe it's not murder.
（女性 自杀 百年纪念路）
1981年 康斯坦斯·韦尔奇 24岁
This was 1981. Constance Welch, 24 years old,
从西尔韦尼亚大桥跳下 淹死在河里
jumps off Sylvania Bridge, drowns in the river.
- 有没有说她为何自杀 - 有
- Does it say why she did it? - Yeah.
是什么
What?
尸体被发现的1小时前 她打过911
An hour before they found her, she calls 911.
她的两个小孩在浴缸里
Her two little kids are in the bathtub.
她离开他们一小会儿
She leaves them alone for a minute,
她回去的时候
and when she comes back,
他们没有呼吸了
they aren't breathing.
两个都死了
Both died.
「我们的孩子不在了 康斯坦斯无法承受」
"Our babies were gone, and Constance just couldn't bear it, "
她丈夫约瑟夫·韦尔奇如是说
said husband, Joseph Welch.
你觉得那桥眼熟吗
That bridge look familiar to you?
这就是康斯坦斯纵身跳河的地方了
So this is where Constance took the swan dive.
那么你觉得老爸曾来过这里
So you think dad would have been here?
他也在查这件事 而我们在寻找他
Well, he's chasing the same story, and we're chasing him.
好 那现在该怎么做
Okay, so now what?
现在我们继续挖掘线索直到找到他为止
Now we keep digging till we find him.
可能需要花点儿时间
It might take a while.
- 迪恩 我说过我要回去的 - 星期一
- Dean, I told you I've got to get back by… - Monday.
对 有个面试
Right. The interview.
- 是的 - 我忘了
- Yeah. - Yeah, I forgot.
你是认真的 是不是
You're really serious about this, aren't you?
你觉得你可以顺利当上律师
You think you're just gonna become some lawyer,
然后娶你的女友
marry your girl?
也许吧 有何不可
Maybe. Why not?
杰西卡知道事实真相吗
Does Jessica know the truth about you?
她知道你做过的这些事吗
Does she know about the things you've done?
不 她永远不需要知道
No, and she's not ever going to know.
真是太好了
Well, that's healthy.
你能假装这是你想要的一切 萨姆
You can pretend all you want, Sammy,
但是你迟早必须面对真实的自我
but sooner or later you're gonna have to face up to who you really are.
你说我是什么
Who is that?
- 我们中的一员 - 不
- One of us. - No!
我与你们不同 我不要过这样的生活
I'm not like you. This is not going to be my life.
- 你有责任的 - 对老爸吗
- Well, you have a responsibility. - To dad?
和他的圣战事业
And his crusade?
如果没有照片 我甚至不知道妈妈的模样
If it weren't for pictures, I wouldn't even know what mom looks like.
有什么用呢
What difference would it make?
即使我们找到杀她的那东西
Even if we do find the thing that killed her,
妈妈也走了 不会再回来了
mom's gone, and she isn't coming back.
不准那样说她
Don't talk about her like that.
萨姆
Sam.
- 她到哪里去了 - 我不知道
- Where'd she go? - I don't know.
- 这他妈… - 谁在开你的车
- What the…? - Who's driving your car?
快 迪恩 赶紧跑 快
Come on, Dean. Let's go! Go!
迪恩
Dean!
什么事
What?!
你还好吧
Hey, are you all right?
好极了
I'm super.
车没事吧
Car all right?
恩 不管她对它做过什么
Yeah, whatever she did to it,
至少它现在没事
it seems all right now.
那康斯坦斯真是个贱人
That Constance chick… what a bitch!
可以肯定的是 她不想我们追查下去
Well, she doesn't want us digging around, that's for sure.
我们现在往哪里追呢 大天才
So where's the trail go from here, genius?
你闻起来像马桶
You smell like a toilet.
一个间房 谢谢
One room, please.
你们来搞家庭聚会还是怎么的
You guys having a reunion or something?
什么意思
What do you mean?
另一个家伙 伯特·阿法米安
That other guy, Bert Aframian.
他在这里租了整月的房间
He came in and bought out a room for the whole month.
我想他至少有几天没回来过了
I don't think he's been here for a couple days at least.
盐 猫眼贝
Salt, cat's-eye shells…
他很担心 设法阻止什么东西进来
He was worried, trying to keep something from coming in.
有什么发现
What do you got here?
百年纪念公路的受害者
Centennial Highway victims.
我不明白了
I don't get it.
我意思是不同人
I mean, different men,
不同工作 年纪 种族
different jobs, age, ethnicities.
他们之间总该有个联系 对吧
There's always a connection, right?
这些人的共性是什么
What do these guys have in common?
（白衣女鬼）
老爸弄明白了
Dad figured it out.
什么意思
What do you mean?
他也找到了我们看过的那篇报道
He found the same article we did.
康斯坦斯·韦尔奇 她是白衣女鬼
Constance Welch. She's a woman in white.
你这狡猾的家伙
You sly dogs.
那好 如果我们要对付的是白衣女鬼
All right, so if we're dealing with a woman in white,
老爸就该已经找到她的尸体并销毁了
dad would have found the corpse and destroyed it.
她可能另有弱点
She might have another weakness.
不 老爸一定会永绝后患
No, dad would want to make sure.
他会挖出她尸骸
He'd dig her up.
有说她埋在哪里吗
Does it say where she's buried?
没 我没找到
No, not that I can tell.
我要是老爸的话 我会去问她丈夫
If I were dad, though, I'd go ask her husband,
如果他还活着
if he's still alive.
好 你何不查下他地址
All right, why don't you see if you can find an address?
我去洗个澡清理下
I'm gonna get cleaned up.
迪恩 之前我说的那些关于爸妈的话
Hey, Dean, what I said earlier about mom and dad…
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
可别和我玩煽情
No chick-flick moments.
好吧 糙人
All right… jerk.
贱人
Bitch.
是我 已经10点20分了…
Hey, it's me. It's about 10:20…
哥们 我饿了
Hey, man. I'm starving.
我要上街弄点吃的去
I'm gonna grab a little something to eat at that diner down the street.
你要带点什么吗
You want anything?
不用了
No.
阿法米安买单哦
Aframian's buying.
快点回来 好吗 我爱你
So come home soon, okay? I love you.
怎么了
What?
兄弟 警察来了 快走
Dude, five-O. Take off.
你怎么办
What about you?
他们发现我了 快去找老爸
Uh, they kind of spotted me. Go find dad.
长官 有何贵干
Problem, officers?
你的搭档呢
Where's your partner?
搭档 什么 什么搭档
Partner? What? What partner?
假冒美国警察 伪造信用卡
So fake U.S. Marshal, fake credit cards.
你什么才是真的
You got anything that's real?
胸咯
My boobs.
你有权保持缄默
You have the right to remain silent.
你准备告诉我们你的真实姓名了吗
So you want to give us your real name?
我告诉过你的 我叫纽金特
I told you. It's Nugent,
特德·纽金特
Ted Nugent.
看来你还没明白你惹上了多大的麻烦
I'm not sure you realize just how much trouble you're in here.
您指的是 一般般的小麻烦
We're talking, like, misdemeanor kind of trouble.
还是「叫得像杀猪」的大麻烦
or "Squeal like a pig" trouble?
你的墙上贴有10名失踪者的照片
You got the faces of 10 missing persons taped to your wall,
还有一大堆邪恶巫术
along with a whole lot of satanic mumbo jumbo.
你现在是正式的嫌犯了
Boy, you are officially a suspect.
真有道理 第一起失踪案发生在82年
That makes sense because when the first one.
我当时只有3岁
went missing in '82, I was 3.
我知道你有同伙 其中一个较为年长
I know you got partners. One of them's an older guy.
或许他就是始作俑者
Maybe he started the whole thing.
所以告诉我 迪恩
So tell me, Dean…
这是他的吗
Is this his?
我想那可能是你的名字
I thought that might be your name.
我翻阅了一遍
See, I leafed through this,
我能明白的少之甚少
what little I could make out.
我是说 简直就是不知所云
I mean, it's nine kinds of crazy,
但我也发现了这个
but I found this, too.
现在 除非你告诉我这究竟是什么意思
Now, you're staying right here.
否则你就别想离开这里
till you tell me exactly what the hell that means.
- 你是约瑟夫·韦尔奇吗 - 是的
- Hi, uh, are you Joseph Welch? - Yeah.
对 更老些 不过是他
Yeah, he was older, but that's him.
他三四天前来过 说他是个记者
He came by three or four days ago, said he was a reporter.
对的 我们合力写篇报道
That's right. We're working on a story together.
我不知道你们要写哪种报道
Well, I don't know what the hell kind of story.
他问我的那些问题
you're working on… the questions he asked me.
关于你已故的妻子 康斯坦斯
About your late wife, Constance.
他问过我她埋在何处
He asked me where she was buried.
你能再说一次在哪里吗
And where is that again?
什么 这种事你要我说两次
What? I got to go through these twice?
如果你不介意 我想核实一下
It's fact checking, if you don't mind.
在布雷肯里奇我的老房子后的一块空地
In a plot behind my old place over on Breckenridge.
你为何要搬家
Why did you move?
我不想住在我孩子们死去的房子里
I'm not gonna live in the house where my children died.
韦尔奇先生 你有再婚吗
Mr. Welch, did you ever marry again?
不可能 康斯坦斯 她是我毕生最爱
No way. Constance… She was the love of my life,
我所认识最美丽的女子
prettiest woman I ever known.
这么说你的婚姻美满
So you had a happy marriage?
那当然
Definitely.
就这样 谢谢你腾出宝贵时间
Well, that should do it. Thanks for your time.
韦尔奇先生 你有听说过白衣女鬼吗
Mr. Welch, you ever hear of a woman in white?
什么
A what?
白衣女鬼或哭泣女鬼
A woman in white or sometimes a weeping woman.
这是个鬼故事
It's a ghost story.
其实是一种现象
Well, it's more of a phenomenon, really.
一种鬼魂 几百年来不断有人撞见
They're spirits. They've been sighted for hundreds of years,
比如夏威夷和墨西哥的很多地方
dozens of places in Hawaii and Mexico,
最近在亚利桑那州和印第安纳州
lately in Arizona, Indiana.
每个都是不同的女子 你懂我的意思吧
All these are different women, you understand,
但她们有共同的经历
but all share the same story.
我不关心这些无稽之谈
Boy, I don't care much for nonsense.
她们在世的时候
You see, when they were alive,
她们的丈夫都曾对她们不忠
their husbands were unfaithful to them,
然后这些女子
and these women,
在短暂的精神错乱中
basically suffering from temporary insanity,
杀死了自己的孩子
murdered their children.
接着 一旦她们意识到自己做了什么
Then, once they realized what they had done,
她们就结束了自己的生命
they took their own lives.
她们的灵魂受到诅咒
So now their spirits are cursed,
游荡在公路 水路旁
walking back roads, waterways,
一旦撞见不忠的男子 就会杀了他
and if they find an unfaithful man, they kill him,
并且那男子会永远消失不见
and that man is never seen again.
你认为
You think…
你认为康斯坦斯与此有关
You think that has something to do with Constance,
自作聪明的家伙
you smart ass?
你说呢
You tell me.
也许 也许我犯过一些错误
I mean, maybe… Maybe I made some mistakes,
但不管我做过什么
but no matter what I did,
康斯坦斯是不会杀死她亲生孩子的
Constance never would have killed her own children.
你给我滚出这里
Now, you get the hell out of here,
不准你再来
and you don't come back.
我不知道告诉你多少回了
I don't know how many times I got to tell you.
这是我高中组储物箱号码
It's my high-school locker combo.
我们要为此耗一整夜吗
Are we gonna do this all night long?
我们刚接到报警电话 怀特福特路有枪击
We just got a 911. Shots fired over at Whiteford Road.
你要不要上洗手间
Do you have to go to the bathroom?
不
No.
那好
Good.
谎报警 萨米 严重违法哟
Fake 911 phone call, Sammy? That's pretty illegal.
不客气
You're welcome.
听着 我们要谈一谈
Listen, we got to talk.
说吧 她丈夫确有不忠
Tell me about it. So the husband was unfaithful.
我们要对付的就是白衣女鬼
We are dealing with a woman in white.
她埋在她的老房子后面
She's buried behind her old house.
萨姆 你能安静一会儿吗
Sammy, would you shut up for a second?
我不明白老爸为何还没有销毁尸体
I can't figure out why he hasn't destroyed the corpse yet.
那就是我正要告诉你的 他离开了
That's what I'm trying to tell you. He's gone.
老爸离开了耶利哥
Dad left Jericho.
什么 你是怎么知道的
What? How do you know?
我拿到了他的日记本
I've got his journal.
他从不离身的日记本
He doesn't go anywhere without that thing.
没错 但他这次没带着
Well, he did this time.
里面有说什么
What's it say?
退役陆战队员的老把戏
Same old ex-Marine crap.
当他想让我们知道他去了哪里
when he wants to let us know where he's going.
经纬坐标
Coordinates.
是哪里
Where to?
我还不能确定
I'm not sure yet.
我不明白 有什么事如此重要
I don't understand. I mean, what can be so important.
让他工作进行一半就离开
that he just gets out in the middle of the job?
迪恩 这到底是怎么回事
Dean, what the hell is going on?
萨姆 萨姆
Sam, Sam!
带我回家
Take me home.
不
No.
别这么做
Don't do this.
我永远回不了家了
I can never go home.
你害怕回家
You're scared to go home.
抱紧我
Hold me.
我好冷
I'm so cold.
你不能杀我 我没有不忠
You can't kill me. I'm not unfaithful.
从来都没有
I've never been.
你将会有的
You will be.
只要抱紧我就好
Just hold me.
我来带你回家
I'm taking you home.
萨姆
Sam!
- 萨姆 - 我在这儿
- Sam! - Here!
你还好吗
You okay?
我想是的
I think.
- 你能动吗 - 能 帮我一把
- Can you move? - Yeah. Help me.
你回来看我们了 妈妈
You've come home to us, mommy.
这就是她淹死她孩子们的地方
So this is where she drowned her kids.
这就是她说永不回家的原因
That's why she could never go home.
她害怕面对他们
She was too scared to face them.
你找到了她的弱点
You found her weak spot.
好样的 萨姆
Nice work, Sammy.
我希望我能对你说同样的话
I wish I could say the same for you.
你怎么会想到朝鬼魂开枪 你个怪胎
What were you thinking shooting Casper in the face, you freak?
我可救了你一命
Hey, saved your ass.
我要再告诉你件事
I'll tell you another thing.
如果你再弄坏我的车
If you screwed up my car,
我会杀了你的
I'll kill you.
好 这就是老爸去的地方
Okay, here's where dad went.
科罗拉多州的布莱克伯特山
It's called Blackbottle Ridge, Colorado.
听着挺诱人 多远
Sounds charming. How far?
大概六百英里
About 600 miles.
如果我们加速 一早就能就到达
If we shag ass, we can make it by morning.
迪恩
Dean, um…
你不想去
You're not going.
我要赶回去 离面试只有十小时了
The interview's in 10 hours. I got to be there.
好 好 随便吧 我送你回去
Yeah. Yeah, whatever. I'll take you home.
如果你找到老爸就打电话给我
You'll call me if you find him?
也许我可以晚点去和你们汇合
Maybe I can meet up with you later, huh?
好 没问题
Yeah, all right.
萨姆
Sam.
你看 我们又合作了
You know, we made a hell of a team back there.
是的
Yeah.
杰西
Jess!
你在家吗
You home!?
（想你爱你）
不
No!
萨姆
Sam!
杰西
Jess!
萨姆 萨姆
Sam! Sam!
不 不
No! No!
杰西 杰西 不
Jess! Jess! No!
我们有活儿干了
We got work to do.